doctorsintraining.com 2010-03-05

# Privacy Policy

**Doctors In Training.com, LLC Privacy Policy**

This is the Privacy Policy for only the information collected from the Web site located at doctorsintraining.com, which operated by Doctors In Training.com, LLC ("Site"). Your expectations and understanding about how we treat your information is very important to us. We understand that you need to be in control of your personal data. This Privacy Policy explains the manner in which the Site collects personal data from you and the purpose for that collection. This Privacy Policy is designed to ensure that you are aware of how your personal data is being used and to provide you with choices about that use. By visiting the Site or submitting your personal data, you accept the terms described in this Privacy Policy. From time to time we may modify these rules. We will notify you of any significant change by posting a notice on our home page and information collection forms. Your continued use of the Site after any modification indicates your agreement to the new terms, even with respect to previously submitted information.

**Collection and Use of Personal Data**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.

**How We Use Your Information**

We may use your personal data in the following ways:

1\. For the purpose for which you specifically provided the personal data, for example to respond to a specific inquiry.

2\. To notify you about our products and services and special offers.

3\. To enhance existing features or develop new features products and services.

4\. To allow you access to the Site to post your own content or communicate with others.

We may combine the information that we collect from you on the Site with information that we collect from third parties.

**Security**

Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to the personally identifiable information provided by you.

**Sharing with Third Parties**

We may use service providers to process the Application Data. These service providers (including companies outside the USA) are restricted from using your personal data in any way other than for the service they are providing. There may also be occasion for Doctors In Training to disclose your personal data to third parties if it believes, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is required by law, to enforce its user agreement or privacy policy, or in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of the assets of Doctors in Training.com LLC.

**Anonymous Information**

A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a Web site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. We may employ cookie technology to monitor and measure how the Site is visited and used. You can turn off the ability to receive any of these cookies by adjusting the browser in your computer, but if you do so, this may affect the functionality of the Site and the information you can access through it.

We collect anonymous data when you visit most pages on the Site. Your visit may automatically provide us with data that is not linked to your personal information, such as your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times, and referring web site addresses. Some parts of the Site use embedded pixel technologies to facilitate your use of the Site and to track general traffic. We use your anonymous data to obtain general statistics regarding the use of the Site and its specific Web pages and to evaluate how our visitors use and navigate the Site on an aggregate basis.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

We may make content or services from other Web sites including our affiliated or co-branded web sites available to you from links located on this Site. These other Web sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the Privacy Policy at each such Web site to determine how that site protects your privacy.

**Transfer of Data Outside of Your Home Country**

Your information may be stored, processed and accessed in the United States or any other countries where Doctors in Training has facilities. By using the Site, you consent to the transfer of information outside your country.

**Questions about Data Collection and Processing**

You may ask questions about the data you have submitted through this Doctors in Training Site by contacting us at info@doctorsintraining.com.

**Your Ability To Choose**

You can let us know that you do not wish us to share your information with third parties for marketing purposes or to notify you about our own products and services and special offers by opting out at the time that you submit your information or by sending us a written request by email to info@doctorsintraining.com. When composing your email, please include the word "Unsubscribe" in the subject line.
